[
    {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "1+1",
        "correct": 4,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "2+2",
        "correct": 1,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "5+2",
        "correct": 2,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "18-9",
        "correct": 3,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "17-10",
        "correct": 2,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 6,
        "question": "2*1",
        "correct": 4,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 7,
        "question": "8-6",
        "correct": 4,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 8,
        "question": "8/2",
        "correct": 1,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 9,
        "question": "9+0",
        "correct": 3,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    },
    {
        "number": 10,
        "question": "1+1+1+1",
        "correct": 1,
        "answers": ["4", "7", "9", "2"]
    }
]